<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on Hung&#39;s Org Notes</title>
    <link>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on Hung&#39;s Org Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DSP 1: The absolute fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/dsp-1-the-absolute-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/dsp-1-the-absolute-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Discrete-time signal Linear time-invariant discrete-time system Convolution Operation and the Impulse Response Conclusion Related    In this short note, I recap the absolute minimum understanding to work with discrete-time signals and systems. These are by no mean complete, and might not be completely technically correct, as sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s easier to state a less precise statement for the sake of clarity. Now, for a very nice course on this topic have a look at [this MIT open courseware][1] or this [coursera course from EPFL][coursera]</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving fast to contact</title>
      <link>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/moving-fast-to-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/moving-fast-to-contact/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Introduction Deriving the optimal contact force Linear control law CCS? A high-level control law Conclusion Related    Introduction Consider the following problem: a position control robot, moving to make contact with a stiff, spring-like environment with stiffness \(K\),
 what is the fastest speed \(v\) that the robot can move down without incurring large force, assuming that the robot has a time-delay of \(T\)?</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming notes to blog posts</title>
      <link>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/transforming-notes-to-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hungpham2511.github.io/org-publish/transforming-notes-to-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Why? Solution Handling citations    Why? I keep a lots of notes containing different ideas and thoughts, but they are not well maintained. As a result, they are not very useful for myself or for others. It would be great if if these notes can be polished and made available online.
Currently my personal site is made with Jekyll. However, it&amp;rsquo;s quite difficult to automatically generate org notes to blog posts in Jekyll.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
